(Penny:)who should not be
eating cheesecake,
(Penny:)to have more cheesecake.
(Howard:)I mean,
(Penny:)one of those chubsters
even had an insulin pump!
Uh-huh!
(Dan:)I have an insulin pump.
(Penny:)People.
(quiet laugh)
(Howard:)It's weird, right?
A grown man in his 30s
living with my mother.
(Raj:)That is weird.
(Raj:)I thought he was, like, 45.
(Howard:)Come on, you don't think
it's a little odd?
I don't know!
I mean, she's lonely.
(Raj:)He needs a place to stay.
(Raj:)I doubt there's
any funny business going on.
(Raj:)And even if there was,
(Raj:)who cares?
They're both adults.
"Who cares"?!
You wouldn't care
(Howard:)if I slept with your mom?
(Raj:)You know what?
You're my best friend,
(Raj:)and she's in a bad marriage.
(Raj:)I give you my blessing.
(Howard:)This is stupid.
(Howard:)I'm just gonna call my mother
and be honest with her.
'Cause that's
what little matzo balls do.